Money and you, but grin off the building turn this, in fact,
usually take people away.  The boss always wins, the workers always do
repentance, this workplace is dead, today this man decided to blow the committee with his own hands
.  These must have seen advertisements, behind-the-scenes players are so
strong, he was once the Hong Kong CEO of the world's largest advertising group
, is the middle of advertising, facing the peak
of 300 people, even took the
dive juice.  Many people think that the first time can be successful, so
I think this, its good people, the chances of success will be
even higher.  He landed the advertising group TheBeast
launched in a bunch of Taili, and competed for the company's three-band profits directly
sent to employees.  So losing body plays can be company numbers, want to be
happy, with some scholars together to do sharing when this, he said
the company sooner or later closed.  As a result, he was not big without clinics, and
opened 38 paper companies, because he saw an extreme
boss
the company did not have their own can not, what about the people who do business?  You
wish the company could still succeed without you
.  to the biggest difference.
Middle age away from entrepreneurship, is it a mid-life crisis, or is it a
life one?  So we sit next to today a
KK, his advertising legend, HK
Ming, I add flip back some information first, so yeah KK
, in fact, before a very large broad company M there to
become the CEO's office, it was like a few people,
yes, yes.  So ah he Wei Ran was at the peak of
, wow, you helped M there double the profit, iệ
sorry several times.  Then he made the
results, it suddenly threw down all the things this themselves to go to start a business
, and zero start, so I read the book you say the toilet has to be
washed is everything is a one-legged kick so that
was 46 years old.  Yes, that forty-six years old,
over ten years so he has built another of the advertising of the
business kingdom out, now has a whole three 30 thirty
companies under the banner of it.  In this episode, we want
his heart, we don't talk about it, we talk about business
.  The first is ah, I would like to ask you is The
Beast's business model, that is what the model is exactly
, so the second is you actually those perverts, exactly
how was born, how did you come up with this so is your
alone 24 hours how do you find 30 companies
?  However, the first question I actually want to know is this, many
people will think that 40 years old is grown up or framed, that you
do not have any big breakthrough to speak of framed, I wonder if you recognize a
different thing, or say the teacher, do you think yes is how.  I
think actually a lot of people, actually go to 40 years old to start
, in fact, I myself go to the age of 40 years old,
I have been the CEO position for many years, so start to think
what next step is actually,
how long can I do this position like this, only to go to forty-six,
why to say that is such a decision think, the most important thing,
my entrepreneurial decision.  So the first is this,
I was in the old company when this performance was created height that
year scare, so that year with my boss to talk colleagues
bonus when it, on that process is very
painful, my boss also said some snow is, that is very stimulating
me
So much so and so, in fact, I really mean that the
profit is reversed 60 times when I save it, that is, I think it is my
colleagues who gave more to you actually, that means that you gave more to us
, so this is one thing.  There is also one
, that is the traffic accident, in fact, so at that time this I that is
, I and my two families that is, I fought for a seven-
seater car actually, in one, that is the red light stop this
, in fact, I do not stop can not be in a hurry, not in a hurry at all, so
I think that night came so, I think the car behind is a
container truck should have hit it
Well, the most my car is tot set loss so,
but this is my family, in fact, there is no big choice
so is sitting in the last row of my son and my son is a bit
rubbed the butt
outside it, just some, so so, I think there are two miracles
Well, so this means all have not avoided me, so actually at that moment,
actually a reflection of mine, is, that feed, life can be
good.  It suddenly ended without a plan,
I thought, if life ended like this, what
regrets do I have, so, then I have.  Family, so I have
several careers, but my career is not me right,
actually the company is not me.  I've built a career from scratch from Messi
, actually I'm looking for a business, because
actually at that time, I have two at the same time leaking me out to start a
business like that, so I asked him to do it himself, but they
refused he insisted that feed, the boss can not do without you here right, really so really so so
they insist on me so I'm here to
push
?  Notice that if the road of heaven you walk this, you do not walk
, he will give some that is a serious accident let you say really, so
I think this, if I still do not come out, scare, maybe really
die, then so, so okay so I consider it
black I decided okay, we do it with you.  It was
decided at a crossroads, yes, because I am now about
40 years old, so yeah, I have some friends of the same age around me
, they started to have some problems
, that is, there is a kind of existence system like this, they actually want
to start a business in their hearts, want to talk about a career like this,
but participate in it is not without money, he is the
world because they do these things
For this, he may be an investment company inside this he is already
looking for a good income that income is good to this,
is worthwfor him to take a such a
bat such a risk, if he is a
rational person say more he can not calculate the
number why he does so is you if you have to calculate this is calculated
correctly actually really the first year of my company turnover.   It's
equivalent to my annual student when I left. I do
n't make any money by not measuring this company at all.  So today
, actually I have not yet, if you work the part yeah, I
have not found back I in that package actually still
.  So but I look at it in another view because entrepreneurship
is on site for my entire life, scared so if I'm still in the
old company, I think five more years, six years.  I think the top is
so up and down actually really so but actually because I came out
I have been working for 14 years, in fact, if I continue to be
healthy, in fact, in the future to do another ten years, no
problem at all, so you refuse to sacrifice the immediate interests of it,
in fact, the number speed is not good must be.  OK is you to that
if you start a business then this you are long term is trying to build a
sustainable
business then this, actually you actually you
have game, I think really, so my own view is I
am earning more, actually out is you are.
Then I said that this CEO fall back to start a business is the easiest to fail
I actually do not understand the real
working CEO and start a business CEO this is two
different things, first working you have a lot of resources you, so
you mean as I used to save, I add a glass of water to help me
, I don't even know where the water machine is
.  You are washing the toilet is also doing, because what, is
because we are very low-level, often that is the toilet water toilet d
water this will be crowned, that is, the first person to work,
water early to work I so I am the first person to use the toilet, so
use this crown is that the whole eh is flooded, so you
use me to clean the toilet, so the company's time?  I can't help it
, not a section you participate in it So but this is the
working CEO, in fact, every section has someone to
help you do it, you still have the highest decision
Entrepreneurship easy to fail this, there is still an E problem,
many people defeat you, in fact, your company is so big, that is,
my old company is that the leader, so it is the
largest company, the largest company, the biggest person when
you are scared
Wait, so that means no this liver frame right, so I used to
call a phone can solve the problem this,
I have tried actually, that is, call to follow ah this
thing, better you find my that what
he, he will help you solve it so I go to
talk to him on the phone to solve the problem.  So and the initial for example,
we have some that we have done some media other my
old company when how can say some will not accept me you
Booking like that, is the new company right financial
situation?  In this way, I only have to that is a
personal guarantee of this, to
have down more books some will.  You would think wow,
that is KK's status is not even they accept
me Booking so there really will be not accepted right It
turns out, I do not know if you have money to pay the bill so and so, but we
, our venture is not using less money already
, but people will be that loss.  Yes, use a knowing mirror to look at
one.  Local medium and medium term, try is not medium and medium term,
are not small and micro enterprises how if you can not survive those that is the
problem of E, you are not too right and wrong, then you have
mental preparation.  And I guess you have a story, that is not
only ah do you count things right, actually I read
your book, actually you are carrying a big
mission.  He wants to see through the company you stretched out
, to actually a social experiment, is you
should be before you observe in advertising, or feel
things that do not, do you hold a few of the
beliefs is that, coming to me to open a new company I have to do in these
positions, I have to break here, is there, in fact, the
most important industry, in fact
, we talk about no assets, in fact
If you look at our company, it means that there are no assets, it's just the
computers. In fact, except for people, there are basically
no special assets.  So but I think the advertising industry
has been to people this asset, in fact, is not too good,
money earned when must share with you, so so my old company is
actually already good bonus so some companies do
not even bonus, but this, throw away a big customer
economy turn this, in fact, usually take people away to fire people so so so
, so long-term one, that is, the
employees of the company
, scared so I came out to start a business, in fact, my one biggest,
hopefully that proves a willingness to share results with employees of an
enterprise, are survivable, scared and can
survive well after these 14 years that is four years later I
think really practical.  So to say yes, I think the
experiment was successful, so I think that is not only surviving is actually
far beyond my initial imagination 添, in fact, I did not think it was to the
scale it is today.  Yes, actually we are now in
this is the
company under the banner of one of TheBeast's other companies so, he is very special right is
this he does not divide the people under his banner into different, but he
will break down different companies.  And have said that
oh the ideal is a company will not exceed people
, so you can
talk when you can talk higher yeah, so now is
born out of 30 companies in our own, that is, when I
talk to you, oh look this TheB now has
34, but you correct back I
said now you have three meetings, we do not catch up
Speed, I want to know how you came up with this set of operating models
.  Well, actually, I would not say that I have such a red
committee, that is, when I first started my business, thought of this
model so I actually came out to start a
business when I started my first company is doing digital market
.  Do you doubt life.  That is there,
actually there, actually I was thinking alas, actually how to do it
actually really so but this in the second year of my business there was
a different team this came to me, wow, so want to
be in cooperation with me so start a business right, so, so I
opened a second company.  But I want to know, that's what you just
said about the first year, already that does not care on the shelf right, it
only caught up with you just then that income crime is the whole
company's profit.  How are you going?
ion, that is, let me open two more.  Uh, no at all
, no such idea, actually really, that maybe the
idea I proposed at the time, in the advertising industry is
relatively new, so they think that, he, right, fought so many
companies, in fact, no company or so willing to
share with employees like that.  Start your own business, maybe the
risk will reach greater so, plus he really
quite agree with my philosophy, so want to be low in our group, so so
, I just started a business when not b this that
y OK?
The holding company then
invests in new ones.  The company then opened and opened so it opened until now
eight companies like that so so good.  However, we are all
very small companies, actually that is exactly what you just said,
actually that is
not more than people, in fact, we actually we are now
probably 170 people, the whole group.  So
our sand company that is on average this less than 5 people per
company so, if most companies are actually 4 to 6
people, and these this
profitable some of the companies you.  Can I
listen to this, are there any early
companies you mantored or invested in?  They and
themselves very now have to very accomplished company.  Oh
so the first company I started actually started with four people,
OK, so this is close to 20 people right?  It's the company you've worked with
, it's been open for a few years, it's been open for 14 years, it's been
open in 2012 until now, such a large company is
less scare so, other companies are more than ten people, but
I see success is not based on the number of people, in fact, it depends on that
, that is, that profitability and that is doing their
advertising work
I would measure some of the criteria for his success to the scare, so I actually
a lot of very successful companies are four or six people of me these companies.
Can you explain
what are the advantages of so such a formation?  What about
when you just entered?  That I'm working in a company is a medium-sized
advertising agency probably means 80 people, this day and
age, in fact, these 20 people are already very large company
, so 4 to, to 6 people is actually quite a ha, why
?  Because actually that technology is solving a lot of problems,
that is, wow, 10 or 20 people do things now maybe one
person can do it already so second is actually this whole
plum industry environment is different, in fact, in my
era, not to mention era, actually I just started the era  It
has exceeded the traditional will frame, that is, accounting for the share of advertising
, this environment also makes it, in fact, very water
changes, actually very water, you are very flooded, advertising
camp is very different from before, that's how it used to be
, that is, doing an advertisement is already back to business,
so this may be the same budget, you
have to dismantle a lot of different things
Until before similar business, because of this sliced, in fact,
our that is from the customer of the budget this, in fact, that may be
falling seven or eight or not already each order
of the bud is washed a lot.  So actually it was not
so much, in fact, the world company is playing this so that is the
advantage
I I describe the home is a similar ice age will solve it,
technology development AI development so this actually the market
environment great changes, so and large companies, in fact, is a that is
quite large kind of, so as the ice period D Long's
death can survive, but now the lizard can survive.  So so
this I think this our such model has the benefits of it, it is
very adaptable, such as the epidemic, that is
actually a lot of event companies, scared so but in
fact, our event company that year is more
than doubled.  why?  Because they are actually the first
company to do some virtuallevent,
said once the epidemic came so that the physical can not do the
event so only do it so, so he did not
turn many physical events to do a couple of times start
people see ah fruitful right, then many customers find you so
Yes, some businesses, maybe their own people robbing children, will
have such conditions.  So there must be.  So how to deal with
these have they want to be oh, that is to increase their itself
actually, yes, there are
spicy to tell the truth, actually, we have a lot more customers this
actually, because that is Brit so many companies, so he
goes out to find different companies to pit a
project, so actually he will say eh better
, I come to find The so that you give three companies actually
suitable for me to do this  The
advantage is that because they are low in BB he will have these
opportunities instead, if he is not under this group,
instead he does not even have these opportunities like that, we do
not constitute as a dart, because this, that is, we are very
transparent to let the customers know that we
are the same group, scare that three different companies,
and the three companies are very independent, operating so independently
This is the boss, actually that is, only has
shares in his own company, so he is fighting for himself, all of it
.  Think this one thing in
performance, how big a difference it
, fighting for yourself and working.  There's a long way to go. That's a
long way.  You see if there is an example, you look at the previous company
, everyone is working, even yourself may be yes
, your strength I do not know if you have a difference, haha ​​so when you
come out to start a business, in fact, you see the biggest difference
will.  However, I actually I mean well, I mean I
do it as my own business when I work, so this I didn't at that time
the profit point rose 60 times or so, it's actually stupid
.  [Laughter] Actually really, you every time you
do a good job every time, in fact, next year your
target will increase, so doing dolls
?  In fact, it should be tight to the target even
, if you find that it is not the target, you quickly
let go of your hands and feet?  Having him have such a bad do so
hard to come next year again chase over the average person is supposed to do this,
but because I am interested in doing business mouth it, so
I really consider their own business so doing the biggest difference between working people and doing business
.  Business people you
want the company to work, you hope the company
can still succeed without you, so this is the
biggest difference, so so the working people, is
how to save his own assets, that is, the
company is not able to do it.  Power yeah those who say yes, or
how to make themselves that, that is Kazeoka d or
more beautiful, yeah, so find more people to help me do things and so on
.  So you that strategy when you start a company is to
make all the people you hired back this becomes that is a real
stakeholder.  So you will because
earlier we did not say to the audience, is that you are in that ten
dollar company, in fact, you are investing for them to start a company
yes that they can become hold, so you can
for yourself.  That is, although the battle of hold 5% or
more, that is, we have to be a large shareholder of so, but
, my partner will have shares like this
, so their shares can be, that is, ten or twenty to
upto 49%.  This part actually I want to
flip some may not have, is you can explain a three this
one thing?  Well, life is a
plan of the multiplication of our that is.  So this we three this is that when the Chinese public
money earns this three parts to the employees, three parts one shareholder,
and then three parts left back to the company to do, that is some that is
stable funds like that.  Did anyone tell you that you did when you first wanted to follow this set of
systems?  It's so no
, because actually this is this thing is not mine, in fact, so is
Ah Private Clear, in fact, he is in Zhongyuan ah in AM730
is running this set, so so when I start a business
, I want to use some of his philosophy right, so so let's
say you have a little share better, so
not just that like I used your set
Not given back the, that is royoty pool for you so and so
, I think he has some shares like that, like that is Ming Zheng Yan Shun D so
, so he let him into such.
In fact, I have interviewed Y La in several episodes before, I have
interviewed it, in fact, until today I interviewed you, you have
overlapped some ideas of, that is,
we have to taste our taste, because they are the most
important asset people in the company
.  Is it really that easy in Hong Kong if you want to
implement this one thing?  There is
no need to
think carefully about this one company is not suitable to do this one thing, and to
apply this set in your own company when it
, and there are some special things to be careful to deal with so I
think to walk here division and system, in fact, that is,
any industry can, but I think if you want to achieve good results,
this is that the industry itself
will be high, if your performance in the industry itself will be high
Fighting advantage is zero your team of people employees if this, in fact,
this set that that is irritating that initiative ye productivity ye creation
ye so the component will be higher, that is as real
estate companies actually actually actually the largest asset is their land asset so it, so so they will think about how to use these
assets effectively.  So so here
our performance yeah, our that is the competitive advantage is going to be
better than some companies that are not willing to share the results with their employees.  Can I listen to
you in this set of systems to the early days of establishment? Then some
people come to see him. When he heard such a
package, their reactions are some of them
love or feel that there is no such advantage, that is,
my early entrepreneurship, in fact, I have been constantly talking about our
points and systems
Speaking yeah, would that mean that spoiled colleagues yeah that thing
?  I think it's not the division and system, division and system
are money to earn, first with him divided right, instead of some that is
employee profit that aspect, instead of this know, that is, there are many
people have other learn together to do sharing time, he said
our company sooner or later to close, you really give some such great employees then
, there are some great things called so called
me perverted employees in the early days
We were that there are several things, so the first is to have two
days of birthday leave, so buy losing body movies can be that company
numbers so I no one has no heart I see free to see, watch movies I
free, you see quite well [laughter], yes and our
line OT more, so ah OT rice is yours
he eats so, so that is because we think that  Every
day I hope to eat more professionally, have to look at the face d scare
so that eat that is better so that, you can eat better if you want to eat better
.  So in addition this each at the same time every
year has 3000 dollars can not live for you to see the show so,
but this we because the company grew after the actual,
began to have some changes that some I was very let go of such is not
very manageable, so the colleagues are that there are some new
companies actually they become spicy after this not completely follow
, but that canceled, for example, see some companies  The
money for the concert, so not to mention this I put that money in to give
them to exercise, that is, they do it, that is, the
fees for those members, so, so
, so there are different variations, so, that for example,
I say two days off, but in short, some companies they say,
in fact, so my so-so
, so-and-so
This now actually means to release together.  Now from now on some
companies are still
changing, so some of this is already that has changed, but this
is the central idea that has not changed, that is, it is
better for employees.  I discuss it with many people, especially
some scholars think why we would make, that he thinks
we continue to premature execution this, because of feeding, your appointment of the cause of
talk, that is, holding him talk to the end.  Yes, with may be
abusive yeah get you that will that have money to earn money to lose money so and so
, but this I have been walking for so many years is good, in fact, that
this we opt d rice money, in fact, should be all
companies are arbitrary
to open some such benefits.  What if you trust someone
?  It will become more trust
worthy, okay, I think some people this,
always wish to stay in people's minds like.  So so
this I tell him I trust you?  You will not disappoint me
, that all the rules,
yes, that we have been walking for so many years really, because we
these employees profit of the expenditure is very manage
, in fact, really is looking for two accounts of the scare, so that will
not affect that we let the employees will handle the grain or so
.  Amreturn do you think the replacement has something, that is,
for example, replaced what yeah so, we actually just look at we have
seen really that is compared to a lot.  Without these some employee
benefits, did not intend to raise the company profitable with employees
, that is, as I actually
work when this, we Global this, actually it to
our margin are margin
15, so but we have 5 years to do actually, so but
this, actually I started 14 years, our lowest that
year openingmargin this is,
in fact, we are talking about a lot of sixteen
20%, if the calculation can not calculate this number of actually,
why the cost is high this is going to make more money this actually so, but
because your costs are invested to employees on this, you found some
good employees over.  He does a lot of motivation he is willing to help
you fight this, in fact, it comes out of the effect is.  That
difference is scary.  You don't go to meet yourself
, that is, if you come.  I won't won't won't
, I haven't done it for a long time, actually really that means I'm
putting me those that he sees so actually this whole group
.  Only the employee light is what I see, because it is what he does and
that aspect so that is me that he is my report
, so in what I see so this in addition this is every
company's actually he is an employee those are all I met back
, actually are called, so they they find me, so we
talk so scared so, so I only see those
employees, that is not part of the employees
One is I've seen it, so there's something to say ah I'm on, did he
say it must have passed which few levels or he showed something
for you to see this you will feel OK? Okay, I'll go with you
, the most fundamental and most
important one principle?  That's what he has to agree with that set of
ideas.
So that means if you that sometimes this that is the communist is tolerating the communist scare
, make small money when, divide out money this may not actually be
so meat feet of so, but that I will tell him, feed the future very
successful you earn a tens of millions of profit
when you divided millions out right, so, so you will not
feel very meat
ella so you have to that you really have to recognize the idea of ​​​​so there
Yes, we a, actually really that is right you just said
overlap must have the scare, but I require
him to have a certain company with my system, so the
nature of the business even if the same, I said my sister
principle is you have to use a sentence to say where your company
differs from other companies?  This will become more and more
difficult your several is getting more difficult, more and more difficult, but
of course better, that is, for example, event company has
two that is, so you have to have
defense is not difficult
, so you can think of easier
comparison, but advertising companies are many, so, I may say more than a
dozen companies
It's the difference in the customer based on it, the
difference in the style of your advertising, how the idea you talk about creativity is
how it can't have some difference like that.  Have you ever had a T-order
?  Oh, there's big ју.  Do you have more orders, or do you pay
more?  Eh, if you really have to count should S more, in fact,
my t order is not less, really if eight opened the frame
then my t have nearly 20 should have.  Yes
, it is wrong too.  Yes, slightly more that is accepted
scare, so actually may be with my late
ól, I have several reasons, the first is that is to
philosophy, recognize our philosophy, to have
defense third to have money ah
so early nothing right, really such a profit,
then began to invest in a second so, so now to
this company, actually earn more  There are
many companies that make money, and they have money here for a long time, so it's just cash
.  feel second first second condition
, the third condition is usually not a problem.  So
you will not be helped decide, people get ahead of you, when you
hand them completely I admit.  Basically this, that's what they decide
, unless it's the same values, philosophy that aspect
of the decision scare so, I will have some participation for example, something that goes
against your values.  That is, for example, he started, I
do not want to distribute to colleagues right, or actually had some, that is
employee benefits things, I do not want to walk anymore right, so scared, I
no longer insist that that is you and I early those four pervert
employees, you must walk, but you subtract one thing when you
will replace a new different thing out this way, so I will
look back, that is, there will not be some new that is
Our philosophy of scare so, is nothing more than changed into a different form of
, so I, I think I would accept those, so
but he said, I started to think, wow!  So a lot of money right
, has spent a lot of not saved a lot of money, so the company's profits are
much greater right so, or that means my own
package can add a lot can so, so so
if they are going to this step, then I will that
usually I will frame it.  So but at the same time would you
say that looking at people this and so ah this person has this characteristic, it is actually
worth it.  Or is this worth fighting, do you actually
have a set of people's way of this I do not know if I have a
set, but I believe myself straight can still be,
yes that I like, that often, really talk to him
situation
Not necessarily
, in fact, it may really be just that he thinks feed, heavy snow is very
obscured, so, into, in fact, there is a chance that the
group, some customers will bring them to it.  will you be able to see it
I don't know if I see it out, but I would have the
intuition to say that, I felt that I, that he although the mouth said very
agree with my set of philosophy this I have a question
mark right, like.  Usually d just pay
service, that is not really believe in people
, he usually d yeah, or will say something, you
will see out that he is actually service.  That
is, I do not have a checklist to see, he said
really this seems to be service will not oh, I think
instead it depends on his personal this when talking to me to see
if he is a sincere person, and whether he will be that is not
just you know the flower earning direction or will so, but these some people
are very honest, that themselves lit will, those I will
actually really add points
Do not let me feel he is very good true and his philosophy aspect
, is it something that I think he has a goodness
, if he means that I feel like a goodness
, scare that if you want to build trust, nothing is better than
in the situation to sell yourself, under the bottom talk about their
feet, because many of us are not good at meeting certain customers in the company
, so we have some things  Well
, actually we really I may not be able to count, if
you ask me to do this.  When we are willing to say that
, I find that the eyes of some clients, in fact, he will
instead measure up.  Will yeah, will think this wants the so,
we better entertain the other few are
.  Yes, yes, because actually people are, that is, there is
some limitation, so I as this
, actually I am a lot of, in fact, for example, I am actually
a very i person.  That is good, that I am not
smooth actually, really so but I will feel feed me, in fact,
I am not good at him recognize actually really so this characteristic has made
me will actually will be a lot more, that there is a lot of
empathy, to people, so so it is you see
how you can use more of your strengths, how to
avoid your own shortcomings, so you can work a good can
.  So in the competition how do you look at it
, how do you pay attention to this person this person strong I can feed you
busy, on the factory your heart has officially logged into
Spotify and Apple [Music]
Podcast so listen to this version anytime, anywhere
click the link below.  My competitiveness from that I
think in our industry to have a benefit to be able to see his
work, his work is for
actually are, that they that if he used to do that what so, that is
done out to see that he is that his ability is what so and so
, this is the first hurdle, the second hurdle
is actually enlightening him personally, because I think
actually enlightening him personally, because I think
We have a person's industry, so our right are
people, we d one pass guarantee, that is, when you communicate with people
your means skills do it, that is, are you a
person, so so those situations I will
be a, that is, I value this one person, is that that is called that
you actually
written before the book
focus in the model of large companies to how to rise to the position of
so, if I want to understand the eyes?  If it is really
not a large company of the west company, that is
written writing on the position when this, that is talking about more than ten years ago scare
, then the business to the environment, is still many large
companies more asked to come more than ten years of today's people, in fact, the whole
market environment, the whole business environment is different
.  First of all, I think the
salary of a big company is actually already that is much smaller. Today,
such a large company is flooded and the position is broken, that is, in this generation,
the opportunity is actually a
lot more  The
daily entry threshold is much lower than 10 years ago or more than 10 years ago. The
first company is going to open actually zero can open a company
that the cost of failure is much lower
, because your investment is not a lot of it, you mean at most
two or three years French road is not right to walk, do not have to walk
through the second road
Enterprises, actually you are very difficult to do with small capital so if
you really yours is an industry development, then you really have to
rise to the top so so to rise to the top so you actually my book says
still I think is, that is, for example, you have not been half divided
like this, that is often workers actually say, oh I
do this job the job says I have to do this sometimes
your boss
So this this is making it difficult for you to rise to the position, because you
keep promoting this to a position, you can not be promoted when this
, on that position, is you not suitable to do it, in fact, in fact,
in need of promotion, is the best, that person is
already performing that job.  Go up first.
First up so, so you in this position you have to
do what your boss does without distinction, you have the opportunity to improve results, that is, one of the
things in the book is to see
low to see high to step so, in fact, counter-translation is that in
fact, you have to know that your power is to have a team.
I'm the most important thing, I'm a team of mine because you
follow you in the star team, you can do the position, my own
PR is this, I only want me to manage my team has a
certain employee the team members are very determined to follow me
, in fact, I'm very successful already, but I'm not really the
boss, I think the boss, actually rely on his
share of work to help him
Yes, so yeah, as long as you hand him homework and he submits homework
this, that's enough Actually no, how to listen to them
.  And if it's going to be like you said, then I really need to build a
good dead heart, team?  So what are we going to do for one thing
I hear you really want Ulan.  This has to listen to you right
?  That I think your team is very [laughter], good for you
actually, I have, I think they have fun, for
one thing, for fun, and for doing well.  Yes so at the
same time I have a
personal
relationship with each and every one of them.  So so I think
there are a lot of things that are not metaphorical, and what we are good at and what we are not good at and what
we are sincerely frank with.  Yes, so I so chemically so everything
to operate this company are, for now I think it brings
a pretty good return too.  Yes, that does
not necessarily
come, is that we may have done some very
proud work, yes, happy, a
very very high team, it is actually very effective.  The
advantage of a small company, this is, that I actually
our early start-up, when the company, I can actually
engage every colleague so, but this actually
goes to our 170 people, in fact, really I really can not
age every colleague, so actually I d are a whole right
actually now just so so I this I, I can now only acity
to engage, I can only or have cap
.  I
myself feel a bit of a flash actually, that is for some
employees, in fact, I am lucky with him, that is, in the past, that is,
when the company lived, that is, when ordinary employees,
I have the opportunity to talk to him, that is, more and more
catch him for a meal, drink a cup of coffee or talk
, but now I'm really so less  There is
no way that machine, that is, the organization is bigger, in fact, there
you are like this, I hope I am better to some and to those colleagues
better so that the whole group's recognition mental strength will be
strong.  I recently, because I'm like you, it turns out
I checked myself I'm an I person, and the
head and can not see really at the same time is not aware of the words, you do not do it so
that way, but in fact, I like it, and I like to talk about the same thing very few people, more say the field of tickets and with everyone here and there, I will soon feel tired of this company, but I'll be
tired of the company recently?  I started to go out and do the next
networking stuff so, I'm learning
as a person exactly how to start topics yeah, even now
doing interviews, actually I started two or three years ago,
I think I want to do I have to learn, that I am I and I can
do what some people can do, are two different things.  I can
go to the game that capacity,
yes, tell me back and that, in fact, A KK this
is not deliver, but is participating in this one thing and do not know is formed on
KK is like that, but there is a there.
Ha, I don't know, I don't know if people forgive me for this lack
, in fact, it really doesn't have to be a lack.  Yeah, I don't know
actually really but really, I'm less recognized, hey, there are other times when
my children were younger, actually at that time I
had a secretary so, I told him, alas, so a month
I am at most two nights is not at home to eat.  Then you help me
arrange it.  In short, in short, at most took the that is such a
ment then no longer help me take these me,
so help me push him I maintain this position when working
, really more will, scare so many
invitations, everyone has their own
business, since I am not a revenge person, in
fact, I mean, I do not force myself to do too much.
Ah actually you have a lot of boundaries for yourself
, that is to say, in terms of eh or I go to work and work hours
, and I read the book you have said that certain advertisements if the
family does not like it then you will not accept so you surround you
, in fact, you have set a lot of it in different places so
I want to ask you, because many people just go to start a business
when, he must have many different opportunities.  But I can
see in you that sayno's
power is actually quite big.  Yes yes yes do you have this aspect
of the amount in it.  Uh, as you said, actually
, I said that is if some.  Customers, I think we
do not want to take it, can not take it like this actually also
with me the same words I tell us d, because when you work
, you do not have to choose what you do scare so but you now that out of
business, you start your own company
Customers, actually that you think is very contrary to your values,
or he asked you to do those things are good, that is really you
do not want to do so, you are feelfree to
push, because the market is very big scare.  So you just mean not doing a certain
type, or a certain customer actually out there are still many customers can be taken by
you, especially when we started as a start-up
this is actually a great advantage I over high, that
I do not need many days, I do not need to do all the
customers all over the world?  I can support our company, we
manage is that follow really follow their own rules to go or go that is what shoot what to
take so.  So how will you go?  Polite us here, the
simplest is to say that I do not have the capacity to do it,
yes, that is the company is small company so no resources he does it is
normal, so scared so, so this is very simple
scare this position, actually I want to know, because not necessarily everyone
understands the advertising industry is done to everyone is crazy, is that
this one at that time the observation or what it was at that time
.  The industry in that market is just as
crazy as it is now, which is actually how crazy it is.  So actually that means that
if the world, in fact, there is no off-duty time
, basically open top is a frequent occurrence of a thing to scare,
so the ceremony to go to work is often the reason, so he said that
technology development makes that, work its mode changed,
efficiency improved, so but because of technology this
also produced a lot, that is, AI can quickly think of this  There is
no way to change the things, is it so now actually I shoot the video
out not I still want to change yeah feed out before changing yeah, so yeah so yeah
you record again, so not fit what to do a help you do it like that
.  So originally, we have finished this thing
, but because of technological reasons this actually makes
us D is really very pressed very important, that is to make a very short
time to make some changes so, that is, at the end of a
very short time can change so, in fact, made a
lot of work out of, actually, but those work are
divided.  Well, that is it, are we
optimizing something that is not worth opting
, or are we doing something based on value after the AI ​​appears to solve the
problem of efficiency
?  Many things have positives
, so you mean actually he makes some very valuable
things out at the same time he also makes a lot of garbage out of it means it is
not as valuable as your program, in fact, so that means
people's concentration is limited, in fact, you make more and
more garbage
Will hear this is that now can not survive that, that is very
difficult to get along with that, what do you think, you think it is the relationship
know, exactly how it is eh, you think that some people think the
reason for Zhang Si is what.  Often it's seen with a high
attitude, eh, yeah, I can give an example like this, is
when our company actually has two to talk about what jobs to fit together?  I said, "
Ah, so you're responsible for this, I'm responsible for this, he's responsible for this
, but then, they often say why is it me, why should
I do this? Why do I have to do this at this time?
So when I heard it initially, I was like wow, a lot of
questions to ask me back, but I quite because
he will actually have to think clearly because
I should actually know this piece of work
Is not want to do
coloring, be lost or so, so their generation's growth
actually they a lot of that autonomous space, think for themselves,
so and so, I think these are some very active type of a d
corpse, in fact, this is guaranteed to be insured actually really so
actually this is the advantage, many people's understanding includes I think
feed is not controlled, so, so not
Teasing him two words of magnetic frame right, so, that I usually hear
such words talk there to say that I can not scold it,
[laughter]
I can not let others, in fact, really like this, so actually
everyone is not allowed to actually, that is, we again
parents actually d children you notice, in fact, very young has not expected to
manage the house alone  To
actually really means that he will sing against you is to,
in fact, any life yeah I think really are unwilling to suffer,
everyone is looking at freedom so I mean this is not any of it
, actually have the characteristics of, why that is the
earlier generations of people are eh, that they will be willing to give people Yeah so that
way, our generation is actually the growth of the economic environment
Bad, actually that you have to support the family so to be managed by people
scolded when actually that feed that is no choice right
, because I need a job right, the job can be really next door
job more than five hundred dollars you switch over right, in fact,
we really will work for money, really so,
but this generation does not think you have quite a lot
The really out is to feed, that is, of course, there are some grass
families so, but that is a small number, but most
people are, that is, the environment at home is not too bad, do not
need to really rely on axioms to live so and so, so they have it
, he has a choice under the circumstances why would accept the device
?
They choose a very important factor in the job right, sometimes he thinks the
job will be meaningful, that is, less salary he is willing,
of course, can not be too much so onable, because
there is a job he that is next to the job over two or three thousand
maybe he did not pass it, because he thinks the job
is much more righteous so do something, and I am satisfied with many
colleagues  There is
no money, why for money this company, so if for example, there are
some, that is, the traditional small manager, it
starts to become turn it, how do you think actually how he can
leverage the characteristics?
Things tell me, I never dare to tell people that I do
advertising, scared, because I think advertising, very meaningless
唧, ask people to launder money, ask people to buy things, so scared, that does
not contribute to his society, so then
I thought actually not, that said actually with many
different industries, in fact,
your family and friends what is your family
Intelligent external system can actually see the work through the industry or social
media, even if you are a very
high profession, so for example, you are an outside doctor so so
you go out to do a very successful operation, you that cut
the intestine out, you will not take it back to the house to see, wow, you
see his handwork quite beautiful so that cut quite beautiful so that
you can not do this
We work can have such an advantage, is that
people around us are seen, that may you want him to think your
very creative, beautiful scare or also that he hopes
you, wow interesting right, actually that brings out the
message quite good right, that is for the
society injected positive energy, for consumers to bring some reflections
, or that is exclusive values
, so these are some of the advantages of our advertising, is can
we put down the work there scare, that is also the customer
money we do it right, so I do not pass these things is, that is why
my stand my Facebook there
I have a saying called to spread it right, so I hope really
use advertising can bring some such positive
messages to our colleagues
Can carry those work back home, that is, so that
some and your family see is good, that feel very proud
Live actually they really said,
we help do the warning scare Sony do that on the plane of the
advertisement, because the camera that characteristic is very fast very fast so, that is,
we said, because there is a door very fast, you capture the
beautiful places in this city and the like, those actually
later that brought a great response, so
I'm not so suspicious that many climates that day may not be very suspicious
Difficult like that, that's a great message, actually this city is very
beautiful like that, so I have read the book I actually
one of the things I think most inspired is,
wow this one person four hours you guessed 34 companies so you
are very perfectly solved a keyman
risk that is, I see you are quite heavy this one thing,
from how you can make this company
No need to get it, so I recently actually I
want to invest in this mind since last year, the reason is
because I am not afraid to risk my own Google?
Home after a year after a small town. That means I can finally have my
own weekend and I eh I I finished
work after really finished work, but you are a 38
company people, I heard you still have time to
travel in May, then, I a week, just
turn four days of you are eh, you will not have something
to share with me
Type of questions of, of leaders or right
entrepreneurs listen, how can accelerate KeyRisk it,
one thing actually, I this is one of me this and
I shot this and I spoke to me I do not let people can not follow me
and he said, so I do not man so, so this is
we that is really
I actually very perfectly let it
The company's do, almost 99 percent of the
decision of it, basically really, the big decision, in fact,
they decide, but in very few very few cases under which he will
ask my opinion in that change those situations, I
said my opinion I give, but you do not have to follow my
intention to do it, so I am also
willing to ask my opinion because of this way
After that, to be sure to do what I want, if
he has this power, he will not come to ask my opinion, so so
this I said, alas actually, that is, I have a
believe, I said to let
the person with the deepest problem to make the decision Oh yes, because you are the
core of the most important problem, so actually should you make the decision
, so no matter what the decision is, let me
To they are not that good power is coming to my opinion, I actually
basically this every company, I open an account with him every month
, every time open half an hour to 45 minutes, that is
simple, but if he needs to ask when
this can always find my so, I
welcome, so I also this I forced my own
schedule not so easy to find him
Not doing so well yourself so very normal, because that is you give
them experience, you have accumulated so much skill so
you actually can, that is better than them, so
but you have to accept that something may not be so perfect
those things, slowly this is actually they have the opportunity to do well
so, and this is actually are actually I have confidence that my
colleagues do this, a hundred percent of
their work is that I can not do well
So good
, that AI is not replace people then it
should be no such things happen actually, that I in
the age of AI it can help you do a lot of things well,
in fact, you still do not judge, AI
comes from data, in fact, many things happen from the past
, that is, to synthesize can give you a lot of advice to
scare you, but if you want
, that breaks some creativity, in fact, may still need
people, so below power is, below power I
accept not original beauty, accept imperfect, and uh, encourage
opinions, encourage feedback is not the other must
follow your feedback line is that you just said to
say oh four first must be good once ah, there are some
Very effective you can only 45 minutes you have not seen all the information once in a long time of
oh is it
actually very efficient, that is very system so to
deal with because I am not a control
, that actually that they update how much I hear
more they do not update things I mean that I do
not need to know it so, when you do not think everything is needed
you can know nothing
, in fact, you think you as a eh Todai ake
holder so scared see once a month,
what do you need to know is
nothing, well, more things are needed, but
what do I see every month?
It is through some data, if there is no illness or pain this actually means
nothing, that is walking healthy, so scared if there is
said to see some data problems or the health of the company
right, then it really needs to be concerned
.So if you have to recommend a book to a person who is just starting out, if you
have to recommend a book to him, you will have no
book you can divide in a book to read is I wrote the
business win ah [laughter]
different industries, maybe there are different entrepreneurial models, but
I think that I said, is just talking about the industry entrepreneurial
models
, that is very difficult, a pass read the old, that is,
I talk about the industry that entrepreneurial model,
I think it is impossible to do, I think it is impossible I, I think it is better to say scare
I eh I read the books on me very impact books are what
, scared books actually called that of
people scare, I think this book on
me is actually a big, in fact.
It is to win win it,
this business model, in fact, is to see is everyone
older to your employees, your customers, your your
some rend scare are your hold from some
customers are yours we all have this  On
the contrary, actually, because I am in, that is, that is doing
said when, I have the opportunity to contact many enterprises,
most actually he is hoping to do something meaningful so and
he hopes that he does business with people, is something to gain
, this also strengthens my confidence
Loh scare, that is with everyone that is and employees share the whole actually
, and I really this actually means that you divided more this actually
this company survive students I especially the most you business my book the
book one of the giant how you how to employees employees will how
to your customers
, and employees share the whole business is going to have what a set of his employees think the
boss is good, second really for those customers good, I
think quite believe is especially in this retail industry, you need
former employees, you are very good for your customers
To hurt, to be able to succeed so so, I think
this, in fact, good people to run the business this
success opportunities will be so more why?
We cooperate, willing to make money from us customers, I, I think they are
not so calculated, in fact, because in
fact I also I myself is comparing, that is very important, I
often help people think first of me, I hope the other person as a win to
scare so I do not say to really make themselves to make him win
Conflict I think I think is not possible in my own run of the business
we run the experience of this, I think
is not broken, even better because that means
talking to you, you have said that being a father is actually very good
CEO
Good CEO of whatever stage of career, in fact,
I think put the house in the highest position, so so we
, I am willing to spend a lot of time
good relationship, so that actually we can now can
talk, manage and do father role, actually have his similar
ground so I value with my employees to build a
good relationship, as a
㖡 employees or sweep this I hope
Yes, even if there is something wrong with it, he will find me to talk
together to think about how to solve the problem that is, after telling me, let
me scold to eat death is the same as children Yes, there is no
mistake, that is the same as teaching is this, that is, if your
child does something wrong
he knows to tell you then let you scold him to death, he will not tell
you
in my children
Our relationship is placed in a very important position, I hope every
decision I make, or every time we meet, I will
not, is that hurt our relationship, so of course that means
you say a hundred percent unrelated relationship
, is very difficult to do, so when you do wrong
really at the moment of the relationship, you have to
scare me sorry
Not living that is wrong, really will say
In this account
, very high authority people, but I really do not to
face of actually I really [laughter]
that I am a, that is not too free of the person, so this
I think the power of this is not very important things to come I
myself think that everyone's relationship is the most important, my face
can be put very low, do you have a
moment you put my right to the lowest.
Maybe because it really and I grow obedient, because studying very bad
, I really do not, I think I grow me, I whether sports
study, acting talent, in fact, everything is very bad
actually really nothing special so I think
I need to keep
Well, I actually performed the best actually I went back into the field
after that, actually instead made me perform even better, even
actually this I performed the best, should be after I became the management,
a lot is my most suitable stage for my performance
turned out to be, because I will also be, because when he
became CEO, do you have any EO, eh
very strong relationship  The
average person's closeness and if a CEO's identity to with the
attitude, in fact, the return does not
greet you and he said very god, except some I do not
know if my colleagues, because here several layers of this some colleagues
many, you have some I do not know very well so, so sometimes my
colleagues will be, you even have my name,
but I do not always have to remember
Try to remember his names
Usually my wife says what's up, scare me to say it's
her right for me, what I eat can't matter
, I have a lot of feelings with my wife, I have a lot of feelings with my wife
, she is a great motivation for my career, so,
when I start a business, because my wife to,
although she does not know, I came out to start a business that year can be
completely no income, so yeah, he can not spend money randomly, so and so
, but he supports me to start a
business, so support my children
Relationship is good, in fact, really they even actually I
talk to our J's colleagues, he feels
amazing, that is because his children actually that
is dating them and ambiguous period this has been shared with me
, in fact, that we are that
will talk their doll talk to us
, that is, so this my son in the UK, in fact, we
scared every week, in fact, every week
I'm very grateful yes, my children actually have such a good relationship with me before we
go ahead we hope to have dinner with him, actually really that what
eat is not very important actually I still hope to
eat with them can that is the last words so so eh
thank you today KKspend over zero two or
two hours to talk to us shared a lot of experiences like you so want to start a
business
Say, is it on your Facebook and your
Lin is there any other platform I am in
AM73 my special Lan's oh, well so thank
you today.